### **DEVANG MAISURIA**

404-641-1429 • dmaisuria1@outlook.com • linkedin.com/in/devang92 • github.com/idevang• US Citizen

Summary

DevOps, digital workspace technology, and mobility guru along with experience with a robust background software lifecycle and software and hardware sales. Experience with customer relationships and programming roles alongside exposure to quality assurance, process improvements, and creative problem-solving.

**Experience** 

VMware Atlanta, Georgia

VMware, a global leader in cloud infrastructure & digital workspace technology, accelerates digital transformation for evolving IT environments

### Site Reliability Engineer / Member of Technical Staff (DevOps)

01/2018 - Present

- Building a highly scalable, available, and robust infrastructure to support development teams from beginning to production.
- Utilize various technologies such as Linux, AWS, Atlassian stack, Jenkins, Windows, and vSphere as well as develop skills in a modern scripting language like python, ruby, or PowerShell.
- Ansible/Packer/Jenkins pipelines to deploy and scale.
- Built an internal tool using Ansible, JSON, and PHP to increase developer's efficiency by 300% and product quality by
  having a one-stop-shop for developers to deploy environments within vSphere with the latest application code and
  testing infrastructure such as certificate authorities and Microsoft Exchange.

## **QASymphony / Tricentis**

Atlanta, Georgia

To create solutions for agile development teams that significantly improve speed, efficiency, and collaboration throughout the software testing process

Sales Engineer Intern

08/2017 - 08/2018

- Demoed our software solutions to customers' upper-level management teams. I helped showcase what all our software can offer, speak towards the technical features, and address any pain points customers might be facing with their current testing processes.
- Worked with customers engineering teams to address their technical questions and clear up any confusion on technical capabilities or features.
- Assisted team in the successful capture of \$600k of business from the competition. (HPQC to gTest)

### VMware Software Engineer Internship

Atlanta, Georgia

oftware Engineer Internship 04/2016 – 08/2017

- Migrated old development domain to a new server in vSphere instance.
- Analyzed requirements, develop test plan strategies, create and execute test cases, track defects
- Increased efficiency by deploying Jenkins and Ansible playbooks to automate development environment

# Microsoft Retail Sales

Atlanta, Georgia

04/2012 - 08/2016

- Generated sales revenue of \$150,000 a year in devices and services while maintaining a gross margin of 23%.
- Coached and mentored 15 fresh staff members
- Collaborate and manage projects with all field team members to develop necessary tools and programs to obtain long-term relationships with customers.

### **Education**

Georgia State University, Bachelor of Business: Computer Information System, 2017

### Skills

- Programming: Ansible, BASH, Groovy, HTML, Java, PHP, Python, Ruby, SQL, Swift, YAML
- Technologies: Atlassian Stack, CRM, DevOps, Git, IaaS, Linux, Software as a Service (SaaS), vSphere
- Software: AWS, IBM Domino, Microsoft Code, Microsoft Exchange, VMware Stack

#### Additional

- Community service: Habit for Humanity and Children's Healthcare of Atlanta
- Languages: Spanish (Beginner), Gujarati/Hindi (intermediate), English (fluent),